#### **CURRICULUM VITAE**

# **Sebastian Klimas**

Software Developer



#### **ABOUT ME**

I have completed my studies in applied informatics (I have not yet defended my research paper). I have had a lifelong passion for computer science and programming in particular. During my studies, I have been involved in student and commercial projects, which has allowed me to learn about and integrate with many programming environments.

I am interested in the world of new technologies and the developing artificial intelligence.

In my spare time I like to expand my knowledge of politics mainly from a socio-economic aspect.

# **PORTFOLIO**

https://sebastianklimas.pl https://github.com/s-klimas

### **SKILLS**

good knowledge of Java and Java frameworks

Spring, JPA standards, Hibernate, Liquibase, Junit 5, AssertJ, Mockito

knowledge of useful development tools Docker, Mockaroo, Postman

good knowledge of PHP and PHP frameworks
Laravel

basic understanding of Python PySimpleGUI

good knowledge of MS Excel

## **LANGUAGES**

Polish - native English - B2

### CONTACT

sebastianklimas@op.pl +48 732 573 767

# **Experience**

06.2022 - 03.2023

# Software developer / E-commerce assistant

Store management on Shoper and auctions on services: Allegro, Amazon, eBay and others using BaseLinker. Design and optimization of scripts for online store management and communication with ecommerce platforms using Python.

Company: Stalesia, Kraków

05.2021 - 12.2021

#### Software developer

Software development including integration of start-up's website with online payment service using PHP in Laravel framework. Company: **Pharmat, Kraków** 

08.2018 - 04.2021

#### Service technician

Hardware service technician and customer service employee. Company: **GSERWIS, Wieliczka** 

# Education

2021 (transfer to 2nd year) - 09.2023

Applied informatics, Bachelor's degree studies

Krakow University of Economics

2020 - 2021

#### IT, Engineering studies

Cracow University of Technology

2015 - 2019

#### Computer technician, Technical School

ZSE, Kraków, ul. Loretańska

# **Certificates and courses**

ECDL Certificate - European certificate in computer skills with modules: B1, B2, B3, B4, S1, S2, S3

Passed vocational qualifications E.12, E.13 and E.14, which make up the title IT Technician

"Java Course", "Spring Course" and "Unit Testing Course" at Javastart.pl thanks to which I got to know: Spring components, JPA standard, Hibernate framework, Liquibase, H2 and MySQL databases, the idea of REST applications, application deployment via Docker and testing libraries like JUnit 5, AssertJ and Mockito